<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-09-26T17:01:41-03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Phi-Markets</title><entry><title type="html">Evergrande’s black swan. Will markets recover? - Weekly analysis</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/evergrande-black-swan" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Evergrande’s black swan. Will markets recover? - Weekly analysis" /><published>2021-09-25T00:00:00-03:00</published><updated>2021-09-25T00:00:00-03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/evergrande-black-swan</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/evergrande-black-swan">&lt;h2 id=&quot;market-overview&quot;&gt;Market overview&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since September began, many markets has been mostly bearish. Last week we have received the Evergrande’s black swan that causes a tremendeous pre-market gap on S&amp;amp;P500 and many indexes on the beginning of this week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, many markets has shown recover symptoms at the ending of this week. In fact, if S&amp;amp;P500 does a upside breakout could push whole market on the bullish side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s see what’s been going on in some markets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;sp500&quot;&gt;S&amp;amp;P500&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;S&amp;amp;P500 started the week with a tremendous 30 points gap. Soon after, price went to test $4322-$4333 daily support that was respected. In futures market was seen a nice double test on 4h timeframe to this support:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/media/post1/4h-double-test.png&quot; alt=&quot;800x600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the course of the week the price had a nice recover action, ending the week almost testing primary daily resistances on $4435-$4455 points. If S&amp;amp;P500 does a upside breakout to $4500 final daily resistance during the next coming week, price could reach a new ATH pushing whole market on the bullish side.
&lt;img src=&quot;/media/post1/sp-daily.png&quot; alt=&quot;800x600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;nasdaq&quot;&gt;NASDAQ&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NASDAQ had a quick test to $14790 daily support, showing recovering symptoms through the next days. Was important to NASDAQ to defend the $15000 weekly support, which it did in friday close. Now it seems that price will confront $15442 daily resistance. If price does a upside breakout to this daily resistance, NASDAQ could reach a new ATH carrying most of tech stocks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/media/post1/nasdaq-daily.png&quot; alt=&quot;800x600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;bitcoin&quot;&gt;Bitcoin&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin has failed to break the $52k weekly resistance. Since then, bears has come to play breaking almost breaking 2 daily supports on $49,1k and $46,8k. For now it seems that is respecting $40,5k daily support. Bitcoin needs to do a upside breakout to $45,5k daily resistance to get some strenght and break $52k weekly resistance. If losses $40,5k daily support is important that price respect $36,5k weekly support to still be bullish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/media/post1/bitcoin-daily.png&quot; alt=&quot;800x600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;usoil&quot;&gt;USOIL&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;USOIL has broke a weekly resistance on $68,62 per barrel, mostly bullish since then. The market retracement this week only produces in USOIL a quick test on $69,45 per barrel daily support, quickly recovering. There is no important daily resistances left. Is expected that USOIL will go to test $85,6 per barrel monthly resistance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/media/post1/usoil-daily.png&quot; alt=&quot;800x600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;dxy&quot;&gt;DXY&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This week dollar got a lot of strength. In fact, ended the week almost breaking up (again) the $93,3 weekly resistance. Also has consolidate several days above $92,7 daily resistance. If dollar do a upside breakout to $93,3 weekly resistance in the coming weeks is expected that dollar go to test $97,3 monthly resistance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/media/post1/dxy-daily.png&quot; alt=&quot;800x600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-to-expect-now&quot;&gt;What to expect now?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the short term Evergrande’s black swan should not affect the whole market immediately. The trend is too strong at this moment, in fact many markets have recoveral signs this week. But it’s a thing must get in view in the coming weeks or months, especially because many indexes starts looking now like Dot-com bubble in monthly timeframe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To put this in perspective, let’s see S&amp;amp;P500 soon after $1552 Dot-com bubble peak:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/media/post1/sp-before.png&quot; alt=&quot;800x600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s see S&amp;amp;P500 now, from Dot-com bubble peak:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/media/post1/sp-after.png&quot; alt=&quot;800x600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Similarties? I think so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have a good week!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sebastian</name></author><summary type="html">Market overview</summary></entry></feed>